George Eliot
Advanced Nurturing High School
You want some snacks, Airi?
Oh, what pretty scenery!
Oh, thanks, Haruka-san!
We're going fairly deep into the mountains.
I bet there's nothing there,
like with the island island.
Want to play cards?
Hey, they say the communal
bath uses natural hot springs.
Oh, sure, I've got some.
For real?
Is it mixed bathing?
Hey, let's not get ahead of ourselves!
Hey, someone up front's
being really annoying.
Keep your voice down, Sudo-kun.
Oh, I bet it's Ike-kun and those guys.
Sorry, Suzune.
I'm nervous having the
upperclassmen here, too.
Hah, Sudo got yelled at.
Stop it, Yamauchi-kun.
Yeah, since we don't interact
with them most times.
Ah, what a pleasant nap that was.
Sounds like they're having fun up there!
Sorry to interrupt the fun,
but I need you to quiet down.
You, the students of Class D...
Excuse me. You're Class C now, aren't you?
Then for you, my newly advanced class,
I'll explain the coming special exam:
the "mixed training camp."
It's so cold!
Wow, check it out!
We're spending a whole week here?
Having to live and work
with some other class...
Dunno if I can do it.
The purpose of this special
exam is to use a training camp
to inspire, primarily, mental growth.
You'll be grouped with people you
wouldn't normally interact with,
and live together there.
"Mixed training camp."
As the name suggests,
it's a special exam in which we're split
along class year and gender lines,
then put into small groups of
players from mixed classes,
and subsequently graded as those groups.
Whether or not we pass is determined
by four tests conducted on the last day.
1.) Zen
A meditation test will be conducted in the dojo.
Grading will be based on etiquette and posture.
2.) Written Exam
A written test primarily about morality will be conducted.
Grading will be based on test scores.
3.) Speech
Every member of the group will give a speech.
Grading will be based on four criteria:
"Volume," "Posture," "Content," "Delivery."
4.) Marathon
All groups will participate in a relay marathon.
Grading will be based on placement and time.
High-scoring groups will receive
class points and private points.
But that's not the important part.
Yeah.
What you really have to avoid
is falling under the borderline.
Groups that fall short of the
borderline will see their leader
and one person named by said leader expelled.
You have to share responsibility
and go down with them?!
You might be in trouble, Sudo.
You've got such a bad attitude.
Huh?!
I've been making a real
effort lately, all right?
I won't let anyone from
our class be expelled.
If you ever find yourself struggling,
feel free to talk to me.
But how are we supposed to talk to you?
Boys and girls are separated,
except for at dinner.
They'll be confiscating these, too.
Yeah, so I think we should have a central
consultant for the girls, as well.
Would you be willing to take
that role, Horikita-san?
Very well.
But while I hesitate to admit to it,
I'm not sure I have an appropriate
personality for assisting others.
You really shouldn't admit to that, yeah.
So, Kushida-san...
I'd like you to serve as sub-leader.
I-I'm not sure how helpful I could be...
Oh, you'll be helpful.
Everyone in the class trusts you, after all.
Um...
Sure! If I'm the one you want,
I'll do my best to help.
There's seriously nothing here.
This is nuts.
And they're taking our phones.
I wanna go home!
Keep it going! Keep it going!
Seems like Class A is already
arranging something.
Class C, I'm taking your phones.
I want all of you to hand them
over and sign the check sheet.
Sender: A
Cancel
Accept
For this exam,
I wonder if the groups will
be graded on a pass/fail.
it won't be possible for me to protect
everyone in the class by myself.
I guess that's when the battle starts, huh?
Third-year bus coming in.
I'm nervous being separated from everyone.
I'll have to narrow down who I protect.
Students in the parking space, please move!
Don't worry. I'm sure it'll work out.
We'll do just what you told us, Nagumo-kun.
Thanks, I'm counting on you.
You work hard, too, Nagumo-kun!
We're going to take our
luggage into the building.
There, you'll divide along gender
lines and break up into groups.
We'll leave the group division up to you.
The school will not get involved.
The group must talk among
themselves and choose a leader.
So they're leaving the whole thing to us.
I'd rather not be in a group with him.
If you're unable to choose a leader,
you'll be automatically disqualified,
meaning you will be expelled.
Ryuen Kakeru.
Since that time he lost to me,
the tyrant of the former Class C
voluntarily relinquished his throne.
Since then, he's been a pariah to Class D...
rather, our entire grade.
Ryuen-san...
We'll start with the first-years.
Get that luggage moving.
We gotta climb a mountain
carrying all that stuff?
Hey, girls, you'd better help.
Horikita-senpai.
Once the groups are decided,
would you like to have a competition?
Don't be ridiculous.
What's the point of a second-year
competing with a third-year?
All I want is a battle between the current
and former student council presidents.
Before you go on and graduate,
I want to find out if I've surpassed you.
What's the nature of the competition?
Horikita-kun?!
Whose group gets the higher average score.
Simple, isn't it?
I see.
I'd be happy to take your wager, then.
But don't get the other
students mixed up in it.
An honorable duel, eh?
Sounds good to me.
There'll be no punishment for losing.
We're fighting for pride, nothing more.
My brother accepted his challenge?
The current student council
president, Nagumo Miyabi.
He appears rather confident.
Hey, are you kidding me?
It's a pretty small room.
So we're staying in here with nine others?
Well, let's all get along.
I'm taking the end, then.
Hey, wait!
Hey! You can't just call it!
Yeah, we need to talk this over.
Huh? What was that, Yukimura?
Don't order me around just 'cause
you got picked for group lea—
I guess that whole thing cowed him somewhat.
I'll gladly take the center, then!
Hey!
He just said we had to talk it out, Koenji!
This is my best position.
The rest of you should choose
wherever you like, as well.
What happened to talking it over?
I guess we've got choppy seas ahead.
Something you want to say, Yahiko?
I shouldn't even need to say it, Hashimoto.
We might both be in Class A,
but I still don't trust you.
I'm sure.
Hey, don't hog all the futons!
But we're currently allies in the same group.
The answer is no!
We'll see about that.
At least lay them parallel to the walls.
That's another no.
We're a band of ruffians,
unlike the other groups.
Don't make trouble for the other classes.
I don't wish to have trouble
made for me, either.
There's no room to form bonds.
I don't usually see you so tired, Ichinose.
Oh, Ayanokoji-kun.
Hey there.
Sorry. Divvying up the
groups was pretty rough.
Girls aren't shy about saying
who they don't like, you know?
Don't take on too much.
Hey, it's okay.
My endurance is the one
thing I've got going for me.
Speaking of...
Having the boys and girls only
get together in the cafeteria...
You can really feel the
school's hand at work, huh?
Their hand?
Yeah.
It feels like a field prepared
especially for sharing information
and giving directions.
I suppose it does.
Honami-chan!
I could use your advice!
Sure! What is it?
The most powerful students here are those
with the best communication skills,
and who others trust the most.
Hey, hey, Kushida-san!
Want to eat with us?
Sorry. I'm talking shop about
our class with Horikita-san.
Oh, really?
Another time, then!
So, did you force me into your
group to keep an eye on me?
Or because you want me to
acknowledge you as an ally?
Yes, I won't deny that
being part of my motive.
I don't suppose you'll accept that
it's completely futile, then?
I want you to trust me.
That's very honest of you.
Sorry, but I don't think
that's going to happen.
I'm never going to tell other
people about your past.
I'd have nothing to gain.
Yeah, you might be right.
If I were to get desperate and destroy the
class like I did back in middle school,
it'd make it really hard
for you to reach Class A.
Then—
Still...
The current situation
is very stifling for me.
If someone put a knife
to your throat and said,
"I won't hurt you, so help me out,"
would you really want to play along?
You're smart.
That's why I think you could
be a real asset to the class.
The others would be more grateful—
Do you not get how much it ticks me off
when you talk down to me like this?
I'll be a good girl for a while, at least.
But until one of us leaves
this school, Horikita-san,
we're never going to see
eye to eye about this.
I'm powerless, aren't I?
How can I be more like my brother?
The hell?
That's so grating...
They're waking us up this early, huh?
Hey, Koenji's missing.
Where'd he get off to?
If we're missing anyone at morning roll call,
it'll mean a point deduction!
Hey, all! Morning!
Is there anything more refreshing
than early morning training?
Training?
You'd better not go running
off on your own again.
I'm pretty sick of your high-and-mighty act.
Rather than chastising me,
shouldn't you be heading for roll call?
You anachronistic idea of a delinquent.
You want a fight, you got it!
Save your fighting for later!
Shut up! He's the one
who's gonna make us late!
You're such a simpleton.
This is why you got demoted to Class D.
What was that?!
Why don't we calm down a bit?
If anything's broken in the fight,
we'll be held responsible.
And if anyone gets a black eye,
we'll have to account for it.
Right?
Now, the one with the glasses.
What was your name?
Yukimura.
Yeah, Yukimura-kun's right.
We're low on time.
Let's eat our breakfast, and if you're still
unhappy, you can do what you like then.
What do you think?
You've got a stay of execution, Koenji.
Oh, thank heavens!
I'm a pacifist, you know.
C'mon, let's get to roll call.
No wonder he's considered
Sakayanagi's right hand.
His leadership is outstanding.
We start with a major
cleaning of the facility.
Not just the interior,
but the grounds, as well.
Then meditation in the name
of spiritual cultivation.
It's only for a short time, but our posture
and etiquette are tightly monitored.
Unfamiliar group activities.
Unfamiliar special classes.
It's only natural that it
would exhaust some students.
I'm so tired!
Wang Mei-yu-san?
Y-Yes, er...
Shiina-san?
Being nervous is just going
to make you more tired.
You're already surrounded with
people you rarely interact with.
W-Well, I wouldn't say that...
Even if they've told us
to just get along now,
it's bound to be a little disorienting.
Yeah, Shiina-san's right!
If you try to climb a wall before
you're ready, you'll just fall off it.
What a funny phrase.
So let's work little by little
to match up our paces, okay?
R-Right!
Thanks, Ichinose-san!
Hey, no need to be that formal!
How about if you call me Mii-chan, then?
That's what everyone else calls me.
Sure. Let's get along, Mii-chan.
Let's get along.
Boy, I'm hungry!
I know. And we finally get to see the girls.
Seriously, I'm starving!
Hey, sorry.
You okay?
Yes.
No need to worry.
Um, so...
I'm gonna go.
Yes, don't concern yourself with me.
Man, Sakayanagi-chan's pretty cute,
but she's also a total klutz.
You're the one who tripped her, man.
Are you all right?
There's no need to worry.
It'll talk to Yamauchi about it later.
Well, I know he didn't do it intentionally.
He just tripped me the one time.
Oh, and although I told you I'd crush you,
that will have to wait until later.
I've decided to crush Class B first.
Class B is a class with strong bonds.
I believe that's the result
of the powerful trust
Ichinose Honami-san has
earned from her classmates.
I also know the reason she holds
a large number of private points
is likely because the class is treating
her as a bank vault of sorts.
But should they really be
leaving their points with her?
Point Transfer in Progress
Ichinose Honami
I don't really think Ichinose's
going to use those points.
Yes, I'm sure she wouldn't.
But every person
has a light side
and a dark side.
I'm looking forward to the time
when we can fight directly.
What the heck was that?
You just dropped this note in front of me?
What if someone else had picked it up?
You wouldn't mess up like that, I'm sure.
Well, yeah, I sure wouldn't.
So, what is it?
You want more of my help now, huh?
Something like that.
I'm about to give you some names
of people I want you to watch.
It might be tough, but I'll try.
Still, this upcoming exam...
It might get rocky.
In previous special exams, I always found
and exploited some loophole in the rules.
On the island, I took Horikita out of the
game and took over her role as leader.
On the cruise ship, I pulled some
sleight-of-hand with the phones.
At the sports festival, I intentionally
stood out to get attention.
In the Paper Shuffle, I arranged
things to cancel out Kushida.
But this time...
I'm surprised to see you reaching out to me.
Do you know why I asked to speak to you?
The Nagumo issue?
Yes.
He already has the second-years
in the palm of his hand.
What do you want me to do about it?
I believe you owe me a favor.
I want you to pay it back
by taking out Nagumo.
You can get Suzune into the student council
and continue directing her behind the scenes.
That's a rather outrageous ask.
Obviously, I don't expect you to
do everything I want just because
you owe me a favor.
I don't have much information
on the upperclassmen.
Let me introduce you to an informant.
The student council vice president,
Kiriyama Ikuto of Class 2-B.
On the surface, he serves Nagumo,
but he's actually collaborating with me.
Let me make one thing clear, Ayanokoji.
I have serious doubts about your abilities.
But I'll do what Horikita-senpai tells me to.
I'm sorry for all the trouble, Kiriyama.
No, I will protect the traditions
you passed on to me.
Nagumo's trying to use his power to
overturn the foundations of this school.
I expect an unprecedented number
of expulsions next year.
I see.
By the way, what about your
competition with Nagumo?
It should work itself out without incident.
How likely is it that Nagumo will keep
his promise not to involve third parties?
Nagumo is entirely unprincipled
in his methods.
But he's never broken a promise before.
Horikita Manabu might lose this one.